Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
You desperately need me
back in there? Okay.
Sorry. I'm on my way.
Hey, lady.
Shit.
I'm launching a new company
which utilizes mobile technology
to connect volunteers
with orphanages throughou--
I'll stop you there.
Our firm already gave to
some green energy thing this year.
But I, uh… I'd take your number.
Shit.
-These orphanages really--
-Yeah.
You know, I'm sort of like
an anarchist libertarian
so I kind of let the free market
take care of, like, whatever
you're going on about.
-Okay. Thanks. Bye.
-You microdose?
-Hi. I'm--
-Probably shouldn't stand there.
Let's disrupt the way
the world drinks juice!
We got a new flavor!
Let's hear it for Mountain Berry Blast!
To connect volunteers with orphanages--
Oh. I'm-I'm sorry. I thought…
Oh, no. [stammers] Why are you sorry?
Typically, at these startups,
they only invite industry people,
so 500 guys, three women.
So they hire a bunch of hot girls
to even the numbers.
-[chuckles]
-Ma'am.
Yes, please. God, get me out of here.
-Hi.
-Ticket?
Twenty bucks? [exhales sharply]
[sighs]
-No, it's uh--
-I'm not in the mood.
You're not Megan Conway.
Your thingy.
Yeah. Megan's, like, a foot shorter
and would, uh, definitely have a drink
in each hand at an open bar.
-Guilty. [chuckles]
-Ah.
I'm Sean Rad.
-Hi.
-I mean it says it right here,
but I think we've established
the lanyards are not to be trusted.
[chuckles]
Well, if you were using an alias,
I'd hope you go with something
less fake sounding than Sean Rad.
Sounds like a rollerblading super spy.
[chuckles]
Okay. Well, what are you doing here?
What are you, looking for free juice?
No. I… The plan was to
make connections for work,
but, uh, I'm new to LA.
I guess I'm not used to
the charm of the tech crowd.
Uh-huh.
Well, they're taking forever with the cars
and you've got the CEO of
the industry's hottest new startup
trapped beside you,
so why don't you tell me your deal?
-You?
-Yeah.
[chuckles] Okay. Yeah. All right.
Um… [sighs]
My name's Whitney Wolfe.
Also sounds very made-up, but continue.
Born and raised in Salt Lake City.
I majored in international studies at SMU.
I-I-I graduated summa cum laude.
Yeah. I wouldn't admit that here.
These… These people,
they prefer the myth of
the genius college dropout.
So just, like, say that you
founded a startup in your dorm room.
I did found a startup in my dorm room.
Junior year.
After the BP oil spill, I created
a company that sold bamboo tote bags
to raise money for the cleanup effort.
Then I graduated,
and I've spent the past six months
volunteering at an orphanage in Thailand.
Uh, but I realized that the system
could be working way more efficiently.
So I'm raising capital to launch an app
that connects orphanages with volunteers--
And this is what you wanna
dedicate your life to?
Maybe.
Uh, my whole life? Yeah. I don't know.
-I mean, I have so many ideas.
-Okay.
Gonna tell you right now,
you need a better answer than that.
[sighs]
Well, I know what I don't wanna do.
I don't wanna sell people
things they don't need.
I don't want to have a job that
I have to pretend is interesting
when I tell my friends.
And I don't wanna do something
that I have to tell myself has value
when actually it kind of doesn't.
Okay. Um, stop by Hatch Labs.
It's my incubator. Any time.
I know everybody.
So I can make some investor intros.
-Sup, man?
-[chuckles]
Oh. It's okay.
Hi. It only opens from the outside.
It's… [chuckles]
-[♪ "Drive" playing on car radio]
-[vocalizes]
♪ It's driven me before ♪
Come on, Kia.
♪ That everyone else gets around ♪
♪ Lately I'm… ♪
-Hi. [chuckles]
-Hi.
-You said any time.
-I did. I did.
Uh, less than 12 hours later
is technically any time.
I can come back if you want.
Um…
Sorry. I'm late to pitch Cardify
to Outback Steakhouse.
They're, uh, actually a really big deal.
Which is why I'm willing to go
to godforsaken Burbank.
Why don't come with me
so I'm not outnumbered.
[chuckles, stammers]
I don't even know what Cardify does.
It's fine. Just smile and act like
everything I'm saying is genius.
Which, uh, won't be hard 'cause it is.
Oh. Um… Oh.
And so 75% of the people
who walk out your doors
do not become repeat customers? Guys.
I mean, this is a problem.
Cardify is the solution.
Cardify is a loyalty rewards app that is
redefining loyalty from the ground up.
Rewards instantly transfer
to your account.
Program becomes a game
that your customers will wanna
keep coming back to play.
Okay.
-Maybe they're working towards…
-Thank you.
…20 loyalty points
for a free bloomin' onion.
Maybe they're working
towards 10,000 points
to share an Outback steak
with, uh… with Jay Leno.
[chuckles] I love Leno.
We can get Jay Leno?
[chuckles] Can we…
Whitney, can we get Leno?
-[scoffs] I've got him on speed dial.
-[chuckles]
Whoa. I prefer that Kate Upton, myself.
-[chuckles] Easy, Ed.
What? She's very talented.
Well… Then you know what?
Then I say we get Upton.
The point is when you can
track loyalty points over years,
you can get creative
with big-ticket rewards.
[grunts]
[groans] I don't know.
Yeah. It just sounds like
a whole lot more work.
Ed. [clears throat]
Think of it this way:
imagine you're taking me out to dinner…
Oh! That's an option?
[chuckles] When the check comes,
do you really wanna pull out
an old, tattered punch card?
I do not.
-Well, with, uh, Cardify…
-Cardify.
…it's all invisible, you know?
You are smooth, sophisticated.
You get the rewards and a second date.
[inhales deeply]
I like it.
What the hell. Let's give it a try
in a few markets
and see if it catches on.
-You're hired.
-[chuckles]
I'm serious. I want you to join the team.
I'm flattered. But you know
I can't just give up on my--
Because you're trying to change the world?
Let me ask you. Your BP oil spill project.
How much did those bamboo tote bags
actually end up raising?
Well, we did okay for such a small co--
Or the orphanage in Thailand?
You feel like you made
a real lasting change in the region?
-Well, no. Which is exactly why--
-Look. Look.
I know you wanna make the world
a better place.
But I also know that those
who actually affect change
do it from a place of power and influence.
Bill Gates cured polio or malaria or
something, but you know what he did first?
He made a hundred billion dollars.
Hmm. You know, men run 92% of tech.
So Bill's chances were
a little better than mine.
Half of CEOs in nonprofit are female.
I prefer those odds
even if I have to start small.
Okay. Well, at Cardify
you'd be starting big.
You'd be our full-fledged
marketing director.
And you'd start tomorrow.
You know Cardify is basically dead, right?
Wait. [chuckles] Wh… What?
General rule of thumb:
a startup has to reach
one million users in the first year
to be considered a success.
We're ten months in,
and we're at about 18,000 users.
Jesus. I literally just signed
my start paperwork.
Oh. Cardify's just one of our ventures.
Technically, we all work for Hatch Labs.
-Right. Right.
-[coworker] Tisha and, uh, Whitney.
Time for the All Hands meeting.
Right. So we're all working on
a number of startups
in hopes that one of them
will stick, right?
So we have this online auction thingy
that makes bidding feel like a game.
And a car rental app that makes
renting a car feel like a game.
And an online dating app
-that makes searching for dates--
-Feel like a game.
We count how many times Sean says
the word "gamify" during the week
and then put that many drinks
on the company card on Friday.
All right, everybody.
Today's gonna be quick.
Um, first I'd like to introduce you
to our official marketing director,
Whitney Wolfe.
Hi. How are you? [chuckles] Hi.
Really looking forward to
getting to know you all.
Hopefully you still wanna work here
after that.
Um, so you should all have the latest
Cardify numbers in front of you.
Sean, we wanna talk about Match Box.
-Cardify is the lead right now.
-Yeah, but look.
We made a logo.
[employees muttering]
I like the part about it being a game.
[stammers] I'm still not sold on
the name Match Box though.
It's too like…
Well, it's too like Match.com.
Okay. Well, we have
a couple other options.
We also, uh…
We're playing around with Court.
Like you're courting someone. Courtship.
Courtship? Is this…
Are we in a Jane Austen novel?
Come on. It's gotta be sexy.
-I actually spent the weekend--
-We really like Hook.
You know, like hooking up
but also, you're fishing for a partner.
Trying to catch them
on your… [whistles] hook.
-Hook is an app for serial killers.
-[coworkers chuckle]
Um, I still like Canoodle.
-I've got Flirt…
-Match Stick was one.
But it's still got the match.
-Just something more…
-Torch…
No, Torch is like fire.
I've got Spoon.
Is that too, like… Just… TLC.
Ooh. I know. Wait, wait.
What about… What about Tinder?
You know, uh… Like, uh, the initial spark.
Starting a fire.
That's kind of what you were
going for with Match Box.
Just adding a little heat.
I don't hate it.
But as I was saying, guys,
Cardify's the lead. So…
[tour guide] All right.
On your left you will see the regal home
of slain actor, George Reeves.
Reeves may have played Superman
on the screen
but in real life he was not
faster than a speeding bullet.
He was shot dead.
They found him in the upstairs bedroom,
-naked, shot through the face.
-Hey, this is, um…
You know, this is actually
the perfect introduction to LA.
Really? Is it? Are you sure?
I was a little bit worried that my casual
obsession with, like, horrible murder
was maybe too weird for a first hang.
I mean…
Grabbing a drink probably
would've been, like, more chill.
Well…
-[gasps]
-[Whitney chuckles]
Wow. Day two, and you're
already my favorite coworker.
Yes! [chuckles]
Not like the competition is,
like, very steep, but, I mean…
Okay, yeah, so tell me,
what is the vibe there?
Like, uh, Sean seems cool.
Yeah. They're all… [sighs] …fine.
I mean, Cardify's my third job in tech,
and every startup is exactly the same.
It's just, like,
a bunch of white dudes not liking it
-when I call them on their bullshit.
-Huh.
It's good, though. It pays the bills.
I make good money.
I get to gig with my band
on the weekend, so it's…
-Hey, you have a band.
-Hmm.
Well, you know what?
When we're in charge, uh,
you'll make better money, and the dudes'll
have no choice but to like it.
Okay. Is that, like, the goal?
-To, like, run shit?
-[tour guide] Ladies,
- you with me?
-Yeah.
-Sorry.
-[tour guide] Elizabeth Short,
-aka the Black Dahlia…
-[chuckles]
…arrived in Los Angeles with big dreams.
Instead, she ended up
mutilated, dismembered,
and left for dead in a vacant lot.
Hey I'm not gonna take that
-as a bad omen. [snorts]
-Totally ignore the last part.
[breathes deeply]
The new Cardify numbers.
Oh, right. Thanks, Stephanie.
Well, eHarmony is my first.
And how'd you find the sign-up process?
Is this a date or an interrogation?
[chuckles] I'm just curious.
Well, sign-up took forever,
especially when the pictures
are what's most important anyways.
Okay.
What do you look for
in a Christian Mingle profile?
An unwavering devotion to Christ.
A strong belief
-in traditional family values.
-Mmm.
And nice feet.
Okay.
Have you considered trying
-any other dating sites?
-Filling out the questionnaire
was like taking the SATs.
I don't think I'll subject myself
to that again. [chuckles]
[stammers] Okay.
So, is that why you joined OkCupid?
Yeah, like I said on my profile,
I'm… I'm mainly just looking
to have some fun. [chuckles]
Okay.
[breathing deeply, moaning]
How often do you go on dates?
Oh, uh, [chuckles] very rarely. You?
Here's your usual.
And what will tonight's gentleman have?
Thank you. Okay.
-Your story was depressing. Had to cut it.
-That's the third time.
I will make it up to you.
Okay, make it up to me by letting me
chase the Bixel lead.
[sighs]
-You know, the insider trading story.
-Yeah, I know.
I gave it to Peters. Here.
This is a good one.
This just says "online dating."
Do we really wanna
report on sad divorcées?
I'm on eHarmony.
Look, [sighs]
we've never covered the topic before.
You can be the Sally Ride
of sad divorcée reporting.
-And why me?
-Look, if I give that to one of the guys,
-their wives are gonna be angry at me.
-I'm angry at you.
You wanna find your big scoop?
Your big scandal? Find it there.
[squeaking, thudding]
-[employee] Whoa!
-Oh.
Whoa. Ow.
-[groans]
-Ow. Shit…
-Oh. Oh.
-[chuckles]
-Hi, I'm Whitney.
-I'm Justin.
-[electricity crackles]
-[both] Oh.
-Sorry.
-Oh.
-It's from the…
-Yeah.
-The slide. Yeah.
-The slide and the static electricity.
-After you.
-I, oh…
-Thank you. [chuckles]
-After you. Yeah.
-Justin and I go way back.
-[employee] Oh, man.
And he's been working behind the scenes
with me here for the past few weeks.
Some of you know him already.
He's all right. Kidding. He's a good dude,
and this guy has a Rolodex a mile long.
-Okay, he could sell condoms to a nun.
-[whistles]
So along with his co-founder designation,
all department heads
will report directly to Justin.
-You're all fired.
-[all chuckle]
No, I'm… I'm just joking around.
This is gonna free up more of my time
as we focus on scaling up.
So, does anyone have anything for Cardify?
Anyone?
-And how about Tinder?
-[clamoring]
I got a little something.
Excuse me, folks. Sorry.
What's… What's happening? I don't…
Fellas, coming through. Excuse me, sorry.
So, I'm getting out of the shower.
-[Diego] Ooh, sexy.
-[all chuckling]
And, for context, I like my showers hot.
'Kay, the whole bathroom
fills up with steam, so,
I go to wipe off the mirror,
and what do I see?
I see this beautiful face
staring right back at me.
I thought to myself,
"Okay, this is fun." [chuckles]
So, so, so I let the mirror
fog up again, right?
I wipe it away again,
this time to the left.
And now I'm thinking to myself,
"Okay, this is…
-this is really fun."
-This is why he's always late?
-[all chuckling]
-Look… look,
in the app, we're using buttons right now
to say "yes" or "no"
to somebody's dating profile,
but it is clunky. It is sluggish.
However,
swiping in one direction
if you like the person's profile,
swiping in the opposite direction
if you don't like the profile,
it makes it all one…
one smooth, fluid motion.
It's organic.
It's how the mind already works,
and it's fun.
-Mmm. What do you guys think?
-[employees murmuring]
-Yeah, I kinda like that.
-Yeah, no, actually I think what
-this does best is differentiate us from--
-Y'know, I like the swipe.
The swipe is cool. But, uh,
we won't have time to program it
before my campus marketing push.
Well, this would be a good time to say
that Tisha and I have actually
been programming it for the last week,
-and it is already in the new update.
-I'll need to be briefed on that first.
-Right, Sean?
-[Sean] But does it work?
See for yourself.
Okay, everybody, uh, check your phones
because right now, ladies and gentlemen,
the swipe
is live.
-Uh, it says I need to update.
-Yeah, you gotta do the update
first, obviously.
-If you just… That one there.
-[Sean] Okay, yeah.
-It's just installing. Do you have it yet?
-Mmm.
It's still… still cooking.
-[Sean] Give it a second.
-[phone chiming]
-All right, all right, I got it. Um…
-[employee 3] Oh, you got it?
Oh, yeah, this is pretty slick.
-[employees] Look, yeah, check it out.
-[Sean] Okay.
-[employee 1] Dude, this is impressive.
-[Tisha] Okay, so…
-Oh!
-You sign in?
-[employee] That's me. Look at that.
-[employee 2] Good picture, man.
-[employee 3] It's intuitive.
-[employee 4] I'm beginning to like it.
-Oh. [chuckles]
-I'll swipe on you.
Yeah, it's like dealing cards.
Hell yeah, JB.
[chuckles] Thanks. And Tisha.
Can we load up some more starter accounts?
So that they're not,
like, staring at blank screens?
I think we should
go with this version tomorrow.
-Definitely. E-mail Brent right now.
-[Sean] Yeah, thank you.
Guys, this is how you gamify.
Mmm, yeah, but her face is kinda beat.
-When has that ever stopped you?
-Bro, shut up.
You know what I'm talking about.
-The redhead is way, way hotter.
-No. No, she's dressed like a pirate's--
-Oh, yo, uh, we're doing the…
-Hey.
Getting some photos
-selected for the demo.
-Pictures for the demo.
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
-Mmm.
-Okay, let me see.
[chuckles] Yep.
Okay.
No, not… not her.
-Yes! Do the redhead.
-[Justin] Mmm. [scoffs]
Whew, she's super hot.
Whitney, you dog. Thank you.
-What'd I say?
-[chuckles]
You wanted to see me?
Yes, yes, I did.
Um, care to talk over a game?
-Ping-Pong?
-Yeah, Ping-Pong.
I could try.
-Yep!
-[grunting] Oh!
-[grunts, exclaims]
-Fuck!
-[laughs]
-Oh, my God. [groans]
-I got it, I got it.
-Come on. Go again.
-[Whitney] Ready?
-Come on, come on.
-You're actually really good at this.
-Yeah,
I grew up with a Ping-Pong table
in our rec room, so…
-Yo! No! No! [chuckles]
-Yes! That's right. Oh, yes!
[exclaims] Okay, go ahead. Sorry.
-Wait, uh, what's the score?
-[groans]
Uh, 17 you, 14 me. Whoa.
-Whoa. You knew I wasn't ready. [chuckles]
-[exclaims]
That's incredibly unsportsmanlike.
You're gonna have to make it up to me.
-Uh, how about a work dinner?
-[chuckling]
Tomorrow night.
Catch me up on your marketing plan.
No, I can't.
I-I leave for SMU in the morning.
Well, then come tonight.
It's my uncle's birthday dinner.
My mom always makes
way too much food anyway.
Oh, what, at your family's house?
-Uh, I don't wanna in--
-No, no, no. [stammering]
They'll love you. They liked Diego, and
he's like the worst person I've ever met.
-Fuck you, bitch.
-Oh, he heard me.
-Whoa.
-Hey, Diego,
my cousin has a boyfriend now,
so don't do the thing--
-Bro, I know. I'm just here for the food.
-Okay.
-[partygoers chattering]
-[Justin] Hey, what's up, buddy?
Britney, how you been?
-Come on, man.
-[child] Justin!
-[chuckling] Hey, what's going on, buddy?
-Whoa! [chuckles]
-Justin. Hi, sweetie.
-Hi, Aunt Gayle. Hi, hi.
-This is Whitney.
-Oh.
-Hi, how are you?
-Hi. I'm Whitney.
Oh, Whitney, this is Ella.
-[gasps] Oh, hi, Ella.
-Aw.
-Oh, she smiled. Oh, my God.
-Hey, what's going on?
-Hi.
-Good to see you.
-[Justin] Good to see you.
-What's going on?
-[partygoer] Justin!
-Hey! What's happening?
-[partygoer] There he is!
-[Whitney] Sorry!
-What's the matter with you?
Showing up two hours late. Dinner's over.
-I showed up.
-[groans]
-Hi. Mom, this Whitney from work.
-Look at you.
-Oh. You're adorable.
-Hi.
-Sit down. Please, make her a plate.
-[Whitney] Oh.
-[Justin's mom] Plenty of leftovers.
-Okay. [chuckles]
So you work with my Justin?
Yes, ma'am.
Been there about, uh, six months.
I don't think it's right
to meet people on the Internet.
I think if you're a good man,
you have no trouble meeting a nice girl.
My Justin's a good man.
-[Justin] Oh.
-Aw. [chuckles]
-I raised you right.
-Mom!
Well, thank you for having me.
Your family is so warm.
-[glass shattering]
-Oh.
-[sighing] Oh, God. Excuse me.
-Oh, God.
-Can I help?
-No, eat.
-Thank you.
-All right, nobody touch anything.
-[Whitney laughing] What's going on?
-Uh, it's chaos. Do you…
-Do you eat everything? Yes?
-Oh, wow. Yes, please.
-Wine? Okay, um.
-Yes.
Pitch me on this dating app idea.
Sean says you're obsessed.
What's going on?
Okay. Um. My first revelation, uh…
Oh, I can help. [chuckles]
Nobody wants to do paperwork.
-[Justin] Right.
-Seriously,
it's, like, make the sign-up process
under two minutes max.
So next is demographics.
You look at your Match.coms,
your e-Harmonys…
-Uh-huh.
-…and it just… it becomes clear
really quickly that young people
are just not using these sites.
-Yeah, they're not cool.
-Right.
It's like you're ad-admitting failure
or social ineptitude
if you have to rely on
a dating site in your 20s.
Wow, that looks good. [chuckles]
I mean, on the other platforms,
I have to really dig
to find any decent guys under 40.
Mmm. So you use the other sites?
Yeah, f… for research.
-Oh, for research. Of course. Of course.
-[chuckles]
And the other thing, right,
-is that they're all websites.
-[Justin] Yeah.
So Hatch's future…
well, the future of everything,
it's just… it's apps.
-Mm-hmm.
-But, at the moment,
we're in the unfortunate position
of trying to launch a dating app
when young people don't date online,
and old people don't do apps.
Okay, you're making me a little nervous.
Am I jumping on a sinking ship?
-No. No.
-What's going on?
I look at this data,
and all I see is potential.
-Okay.
-You know,
if we can just break through that stigma,
suddenly we've got complete market share
of all millennial dating…
-Wow, thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-The demo that does most of the dating.
You know, all we need is just one…
[chuckles] …youthful epicenter
to adopt the app, and I just… I…
-I really think it'll catch like wildfire.
-Mmm.
Which is why I said to Sean, you know,
"Just give me 600 bucks and a plane ticket
and I will come back
-with the next Fortune 500 company."
-That is sick.
-Justin.
-Hey-- [groaning]
-[child laughs]
-[laughs]
-Buddy! Oh, my…
-[laughing]
-What did you do?
-I don't know.
[stammers] Why SMU?
Why is Dallas our-our youthful epicenter?
-Please, walk me through that. Keep going.
-[laughs] Okay. Well, I went there…
Go Mustangs.
So, I know the lay of the land
and the Greek life.
-Okay. Just 'cause…
-Hey, honey.
-Mmm.
-Hey.
You don't have some college sweetheart
waiting for you, huh?
No. No, God no.
Why-Why-Why "God no"? What does that mean?
Uh… [sighs] I just had a really…
-a toxic boyfriend back in high school.
-Hmm.
It's actually, like,
not much better in… [laughing] …college.
Guys suck.
Yeah, thanks. [chuckles]
So, like… [stammers] Are you, uh…
Currently you don't… you don't have…
-Right now?
-Yeah.
-No. [chuckles]
-Oh, okay. Okay. That's… No, that's good.
For the best. Don't wanna have
some jealous guy fighting me
when I take you home tonight.
When I drive you home tonight.
When I drive you home.
-Like, after this. Like, not…
-[snickers]
-[laughing] Oh, my God.
-I'm freaking…
[♪ "Bulletproof" plays]
[pants] I graduated not even a year ago.
Why do I feel 40 years older
than these… [chuckling] …girls?
I mean, these girls
scare the fuck out of me,
but you are, like, one of them.
They're gonna love it.
I don't get it.
[stammers] We throw, like, mixers,
parties, uh, cookouts, and formals.
[stammers] Meeting guys is,
like, what we do here.
Yes. No, I get that, uh, totally.
Um, okay.
[exhales sharply]
Have you ever been in a party
and there is this cute guy,
and you're thinking about approaching him,
but you don't [chuckles] 'cause
you're nervous he won't be interested?
Actually, no. Don't answer that.
[chuckling] You are like
the most gorgeous person
-I have ever seen in my life.
-[Kappas chuckle]
But for the rest of us, you know,
how many of you can relate to that?
Kinda? Yes, okay, great.
With Tinder, you're always
starting a conversation with someone
who you already know is interested.
You know what? Let's just, uh,
let's see who's on here. Okay.
So, here we go.
Okay. All right.
Now this is what I'm talking about.
He's a good-looking guy.
Okay, let's keep look… Ugh. No. Mm-mmm.
But look, he's Gryffindor, I'm Ravenclaw.
[scoffs] That is just not meant to be.
That's a no, so I am swiping left. Nope.
Okay. Ooh, Kyle.
Do we like Kyle?
Hmm. You know. Kinda cute.
Uh, oh, wait.
I'm pretty sure
he dated my friend forever ago.
-Pfft. And Kappas don't date Kappas' exes.
-[murmuring] Mm-mmm.
Good. That's a no, so swipe left.
Next.
Huh. This I could get into.
He has, you know,
nice eyes, decent dresser.
I'm swiping right.
Oh! And look at that, we matched.
Okay, so that, that basically means
that we both swiped right on each other.
And he's already sent a message.
"Hey, Whitney. Love your profile.
Want to grab a coffee
at The Arnold tomorrow?"
Hmm. Sure, [chuckles]
-don't mind if I do, Justin.
-[Kappas chuckle]
Okay, so, what do you think?
-[inhales deeply]
-Did I mention
that Sigma Sigma Delta and Beta Lambda
have already signed up?
Oh, they have been matching all morning.
-Wait, BG has been matching with the Sigs?
-They're all on there?
-Yes.
-[chuckles] Uh, h-how do I download it?
I wanna see this.
-Yes, um, great.
-[all murmuring]
Great. Okay, so Tisha here,
she's gonna walk you through it.
Super easy.
[stammers] Gotta make a quick phone call.
-[pants] Stall them for like 15 minutes.
-They're gonna find out no one they know
-is on this app so unless they sign up.
-Stall them.
Hi.
-[students chattering]
-[panting]
Hey, you guys. Hi.
Um, how would you like
to meet the hottest girls on campus?
-[students clamoring] Yes!
-Oh, yes! That's what I'm talking about.
Okay, get out your phones.
Hey, guys, so you're really, really gonna
wanna choose a profile photo carefully.
Don't obsess over your photo
'cause you can always change 'em later.
That's great.
Take your time. [chuckles]
-And start swiping, guys. Let's do it.
-[students chatter]
I'm not seeing
any of the Sig guys on here.
Yeah, I don't recognize any of these guys.
They definitely don't go here.
Okay, uh, like I said, I don't think
this is gonna be a fit for us.
Oh. [sucks teeth]
[gasps] Oh, my God.
-Andrew Thompson's on here. Look.
-[Kappa] What?
-Oh! And Keshawn Brooks!
-Wait. What? Keshawn?
Well, do not swipe right on Keshawn.
I'm swiping!
-[student] I wanna see!
-[student 2] This is good.
I matched with Sophie.
-And Gabby! Whoo!
-Thanks, guys.
-Oh, tell your friends!
-Hey, wait!
What's your profile name?
Jackie!
There's a woman here saying everyone
is on this app except for Beta Gamma.
-[Jackie] What?
-[panting] Hi!
I love this photo.
Definitely use that photo.
You know what? Just get any--
Everyone, everyone's on it.
You’ve gotta download it.
Here. You put these everywhere.
Everywhere. In the dorms, in the--
I'll do it if you download it!
If you download it, I'll do it. Okay.
[cheering]
Great! Give me your phone!
Download Tinder!
[panting, retches]
Hey… Ooh!
-Hey! What are you doing?
-[chuckles] Hi, you guys.
Uh, sorry to stop you. Uh, my name
is Whitney. I'm here to tell you, uh--
Oh, my God. [pants]
-Hey! How was it?
-[laughs]
Oh! So good.
Look at these numbers.
-[panting, laughing]
-Next stop, UT.
[both laughing]
[ringing]
[gasps] Oh, shit.
-Hi. Hey.
- Hey! There you are.
What's up? How's New York?
Oh, yeah… No, uh, NYU is tomorrow.
I'm still in Utah tonight.
Oh, okay. Are you… Are you gonna
see your parents while you're there?
Oh, no. I just…
I'm too busy unfortunately.
How are you? Um, hey, how was golf?
Did you win?
Did… Yes.
Well, no 'cause Sean cheats,
but if he didn't, then I would've won.
I'm so jealous
you get to travel everywhere.
-It's so fucking boring here.
-Wait. Oh.
No, I saw your, um, uh, USC push worked.
- Oh, yeah. [chuckles]
-The nightclub idea was a huge hit.
Oh, yeah, it was massive. It was--
It was… I, what,
download the app and skip the line--
Yep. Turns out bribing works.
I mean, only losers wait in line
in the first place, but…
Oh, well they didn't all look like losers.
I, uh, I saw your picture
with all those girls. Like, um, they were…
-You're the jealous one now.
-No.
-Oh, no, no. I didn't…
- Oh, no, no, I know.
-No, I… No, I didn't either.
-I'm not jealous.
-I didn't mean it like that.
- I mean, I'd be cool if you were jealous
'cause that would mean that you like me
a little.
And I would, uh…
I would like if you liked me a little.
Ah, shit.
-Sorry. I'll take that back. I--
-No, it's… No. Mm-mmm.
It's okay. I… I, um…
I, uh… I… I do. I-I like you a little.
[snorts]
[Stephanie] Please God.
-[Sean] Looks good.
-Great.
Nice.
-Uh, hey, JB, are we good to go?
-Getting closer.
Couldn't we just put
our subscription numbers
on, like, a big flat-screen or something?
[JB] Absolutely not. This is analog.
This is much cooler.
-Sup, papichulo.
-[chuckling] What you doing?
Really? Okay, great.
I think Sean's gonna be here any minute.
Oh, hey. Hey. Not at work.
What? Don't tell me Sean gave you
the little… little talk too.
-It's fine, he can't stop us from dating.
-Wait, you told Sean about us?
Of course I did. He's my best friend.
Wait. No, he's our boss.
I'm your boss too. So what?
[Sean] Guys, have you met Hugh?
This is…
This is Whitney Wolfe and Justin Mateen.
-The two I was telling you about.
-It's a pleasure.
Well, I'm a co-founder.
I hear the whole college marketing push
was a big success.
-You kids just might have something here.
-Oh, yeah, there's no denying it.
I mean, you put together the fact
that no one has successfully tapped
the millennial dating scene,
and that millennials are the ones
doing most of the dating,
it became very clear
what our mission statement was.
[Hugh] Keep this guy around.
Oh, no.
[chuckles] It was nice to meet Hugh… you.
Uh, Mr… Hugh.
[scoffs] What? [stammers]
Wait, that was my thing.
You were just standing there
not saying anything so I just…
I just… I just covered for you.
Sorry. That's my bad.
[Whitney] I…
Let's…
How we looking JB?
Yeah, just about there, brother.
Yeah, we're good.
-Okay.
-[JB whoops]
-Is it working?
-Yeah.
[employees cheering]
[groaning]
Damn it.
[cheering]
Oh, my God. I gotta…
[stammers] I gotta say
I'm shocked this thing actually works.
[employees cheering]
You know what? Maybe I should
stop being shocked by success
after the past few months we've had.
That's right!
Come on!
Justin, JB, get up here.
-Come on. Let's go.
-[Diego] Get 'em, JB.
I'm proud to have you jerks
as my co-founders.
Whitney, you too.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
As you all know--
As you know, Whitney has been
a one-woman wrecking ball,
strong-arming every college student who
dares cross her path into joining Tinder
-and-and--
-[employees cheering]
Judging by these numbers, guys,
they're telling their friends. Okay?
So I'd like to officially announce
that Whitney is the newest,
and certainly the most feminine,
co-founder of Tinder. Yes. Yes.
Oh, my God.
My God!
You didn't tell me.
[stammers] I didn't know. I--
-Get up… Get up here.
-Oh, my God. Sean.
Yeah! [laughs]
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
Um. [squeals]
I, uh… [stammers]
Okay, I just wanna say a few things.
Um, I feel so lucky, uh,
to work alongside such talented,
hardworking, inspiring people--
[cheering]
Individuals who are also
just my closest friends.
And I'm not just saying that
because we work together nonstop
so… [blows]
…you're basically my only friends.
[employees chuckle]
-Okay, I don't wanna make a big speech--
-Too late.
You're literally giving
a speech right now.
-Okay, okay, okay.
-[employees cheering]
I guess we gotta get back to work!
We gotta get back to work,
you heard her. You heard her.
Sup.
♪ Let's raise the bar ♪
-Yes!
-Oh, my God. Hi. Is it… Salt?
Yes.
Whoa, Justin, that was rude.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yo, yo, yo, yo.
Read this. Read this. Read this.
"Tinder slut.
A girl that sleeps with men
using the popular dating app Tinder."
Urban Dictionary!
Urban Dictionary! Yeah!
♪ We're up all night to get lucky
We're up all night to get lucky ♪
Like, this is a dream come true.
Thank you. Thank you.
-Hey.
-[skater] Hey, Nate.
Come on in.
[sighs]
Hey, Diego. Diego. Take a picture.
Her checking her e-mail.
It's gonna look so good.
Girls, hi. Can you put these on?
And can everybody say "Swipe right."
-[party guests] Swipe right.
-[Justin] Yeah. Perfect. Get that shot.
[Diego] Okay. Hold on. Hold on.
[party guests cheering]
[Justin] Hey! Are you kidding?
-[yelps] What?
-[screams]
-Come on. What are you doing?
-What are you doing?
-The fuck are you doing?
-I am working.
And the winner of this year's
Best New Startup is…
Looks like they're the ones
getting lucky tonight.
-Tinder.
[audience cheering]
[announcer] Accepting the Crunchie
on behalf of Tinder
are co-founders Sean Rad,
Justin Mateen and Jonathan Badeen.
[Sean] It has been…
It's been an incredible year,
with a lot more to come.
Uh… [chuckles] Thank you.
We hope that we can live up to
this honor. Guys, thank you so much.
And thank you for swiping right.
[chuckles] Whoo!
I'm not meaning to. I'm not trying to.
It's just… This is… This is just…
[Whitney] Okay. Yeah, absolutely.
You know,
we would love to keep talking strategy.
Uh, you should come by the new office
this week.
-[Tisha] Hey, Whit.
-Um, one sec.
Can we all chat for a second?
Oh. O-Okay.
Okay. What's up?
Show her.
Uh, I have friends sending me
insane screenshots
of dudes being awful on the app.
They report and nothing happens.
And there's a VICE article
about how pervasive the dick pics are.
[sighs] This is terrible.
So you'll speak to the guys?
I mean… Well, we delete the dick pics.
Uh, well, I mean, Beth deletes them,
which is in and of itself fucked up.
Beth graduated from Cornell Business.
She did not sign up for that.
And nothing happens
to the guys who send them
so they just keep doing it.
I'm starting to recognize
some of the dicks.
[sighs] Okay. Yes.
We absolutely need to address this. Um…
I'll-I'll be sure to find a time
to bring it up with the guys.
Uh, there's the four o'clock
this afternoon.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
Thank you, Stephanie. [chuckles]
Whit, what is with the hesitation?
There's no hesitation. I'm just, um…
I'm the only woman in there and it's…
I'm trying…
I have to come off in a certain way.
It's… You…
It's hard to explain
when you're not in there.
Oh. Well, try.
Tisha, I'm not disagreeing with you,
all right?
I'm just… You are the one who told me
that a startup isn't anything
until it hits a million users.
We're not there yet, you know.
And the more we grow,
the stronger footing
I have to really make a change.
Okay, but are we saying
that we can't do the right thing
until we've crossed
some imaginary finish line?
I just kinda feel like that's an excuse
to not confront the real iss--
Okay. I will bring it up.
I will bring it up.
-Thanks, Whitney.
-No, yeah, you… you got it.
So projections are good.
I mean… Yeah, they're really good.
[JB] True. [chuckles]
-But they're really good…
-[JB] They're really good. [chuckles]
…but that doesn't mean
it's time to get complacent.
Copycat apps are popping up
left and right. So we can't let up.
-Anything else for right now?
-[Justin] No, it's--
Well, uh… [clears throat]
Apparently, um, some female users are,
you know, they're feeling
that we are not responsive enough
to harassment complaints.
And there's also the, um…
You're gonna say the dick pic article.
Yes. I-I think there could be room
to toughen up our policies.
I don't know, babe. It-It sounds like
clickbait to me. Not an actual problem.
Well, I mean, it is an actual problem if,
you know,
it starts driving women away from the app.
I mean, you know it's kinda hard
to run a dating app without 'em.
Look, I think most of these chicks
are just reporting harassment
on guys who reject them. Probably.
-You can't be serious.
-That's what this sounds like.
Justin, that is…
You do not really mean that?
-No. What? I'm serious.
-That is just really--
-Guys. Excuse me. Okay? Okay?
-[Justin] Sorry.
Um, I'm just not sure
that it's our place though
to tell people
what they can and cannot say.
Uh, sure. First Amendment. Right, exactly.
I mean, I-I don't think
there's something wrong
-with taking a look at our policy.
-Right.
We've not really made any changes
since we first started this so--
Guys, we are netting
over 10,000 new sign-ups a day.
That means the formula
is clearly working, why mess with it?
Yeah, I mean, we need to be practical,
not emotional. Right?
We don't wanna get in the habit
of overreacting
to every piece of bad press.
-Like…
-[Justin] That's true.
I mean, is there… is there a way
to confront the conversation
head-on though?
Like, kind of control the narrative
and reframe it somehow.
[Justin] Mmm.
[sighs]
Well, I think it's this.
Um…
[sighs] It used to be that
if you want to meet someone,
you would go to a bar
on a Friday night, right?
And you might get hit on
by the occasional creep.
It's not on the bar owner.
Doesn't mean you burn down the bar.
-[Sean] Yeah.
-[Justin] IRL,
guys say stupid shit to girls
all the time… at like a club.
Doesn't mean it's the club's fault.
-Yes. That.
-[Justin] Yeah.
Good. Sweet. Okay. Nice work.
Um… What's next?
I can't do this anymore.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Are you kidding me?
I really wanna be focusing on work
right now.
-Okay?
-On work. You-You work for me.
Justin, come on.
-What? You do.
-No, no, I don't work for you.
I'm your colleague, okay?
I'm a co-founder.
Who is he? Who are you flirting with?
You're talking to someone, I can tell.
-I have said before, there's no one.
-What am I supposed to tell my family?
My mom trusted you.
-What am I supposed to say?
-I know. I'm sorry, okay?
I know this sucks.
No, no. It doesn't suck.
Have you any idea the kind of
Tinder trim I've been turning down?
Okay. Okay. Have at it.
[chuckling] Oh, yeah, walk… walk away.
-Yeah. You got what you wanted.
-[Whitney exhales deeply]
-Fuck the boss to get ahead.
-[shushes]
Then you drop him once you're there.
Who you gonna blow next? Sean?
Under his fucking desk?
[gasps]
Damn it. Shit. I heard how that…
I'm sorry.
I know that's too far. Sorry.
Can we just go back to my place
and talk about this?
I really did not mean that.
Have you… Have you been in this
relationship for the past six months?
-You make me feel like shit, Justin.
-I'm sorry.
[exhales sharply]
Let's just leave it there, okay?
Let's just leave it there.
You're doing it again.
[blows]
What am I doing?
The toxic boyfriend in-in high school
and then again in college and now me.
I'm the toxic boyfriend.
You notice a pattern here?
It's not the guys, Whit,
it's… it's-it's you.
There's something wrong with you.
You can tell yourself
you're the victim, okay?
The truth is there's a guy here
who really cares about you…
[scoffs]
…who'd be willing to forgive you.
-I'm leaving.
-Really?
Just all I ask is that we just please
keep this professional at work.
[groans]
Yeah, I'll be professional as fuck.
Don't worry.
They are swiping on profiles,
you know, matching with cute singles,
you know, maybe they're even
coordinating their next hookup.
-And as a result, uh, their, um…
-[phone buzzing]
…adrenaline, their dopamine,
it's just like…
It's flooding through their bodies
and that is their state of mind
when your client's ad pops up.
I feel pretty confident that's the message
we can sell to our board members.
I'm so sorry. I just… I really…
-I thought that my phone was on silent.
-No worries, please.
Listen, I-I think we have enough here
to take back to our clients.
I'm so sorry about that.
I was distracted. I, um…
-Yeah. We-We're… We're good. Thank you.
-Um, p…
[Tisha] Whitney.
-[sighs] Hi.
-Come on, you're a basic white woman,
-Phil Collins should be like a god to you.
-[blows raspberry]
I love Phil Collins.
That was Phil Collins? [laughing]
-[sighs] Oh, God.
-I mean, disrespectfully, it was.
-But yeah.
-[groans] Sorry. I'm sorry. I just, um…
Justin's been derailing me all week
so I'm behind… I'm really behind on work.
I just need to send this last--
Well, maybe you should just
take a break from all that, right?
Just for like a second. It's Sunday.
It's the Lord's day.
And also we…
Are c… We're celebrating your birthday.
[chuckles] Yay! Yes. Absolutely.
I'm so… I'm so sorry.
I'm right back with you. I'm here.
[Tisha] Okay.
Look, Whit, if this asshole's
really affecting your work this much,
I think you should speak to Sean.
No. No way.
Don't. I'm… I'm fine.
I'm dealing with it. It's… It's…
I don't wanna cause any drama.
Just so embarrassing. Um…
Well, maybe… I, uh…
I think you should speak to him anyway.
Not just about the Justin thing.
Um. Okay. Why?
Um. [sighs] The… You know, the
Time profile that we all interviewed for?
-Mm-hmm.
-Um…
[clicks tongue] It doesn't
list you as a co-founder.
[mumbles] Wait, what? I can't…
-I can't do dinner. I'm sorry.
-Yeah.
Yeah. [chuckles]
[Sean] Dude, I d…
I don't know how this happened.
I'm sorry. I-I saw it.
It was an oversight.
You somehow didn't realize
you were posing for a photo?
Hey, Whit, it is one stupid article
that no one's gonna read.
-It's Time magazine.
-Look, it's…
Hey, you know that I'm
your biggest cheerleader, right?
Whit, I, like, brag about you to everyone.
-[sighs]
-What's…
What's going on? You okay?
You're usually, you know…
-You're eyes on the prize.
-[sighs] I still am.
Okay.
[sighs] Okay, this is just…
This is not just about the article.
Like, I don't want to make this
a big deal or anything, all right?
But I'm having sort of a…
um, a problem with Justin.
-Mm-hmm.
-[sighs] Since we've broken up,
you know, things have gotten… intense.
All right. Just come sit.
Yeah. That's… Um…
[clicks tongue] You're both adults.
And couples break up. You know, I think…
I really think
the best thing you can do is just…
I think you guys have to
just get over this and move on, right?
-Exactly. That's exactly what I wanna do.
-Okay.
Do you think maybe
you could say that to him?
I think it might be a bit of
a bad look if I were to step in here.
I just… People talk.
I… I just… No, I… [stammers, sighs]
Okay, look, I really didn't
wanna have to bring you into this, um…
[sniffles]
It's got pretty bad.
Whoa.
[Whitney sighs]
Um…
I'll talk to him.
-Okay.
[phone vibrates]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[panting] Okay.
-Did we make it in time?
-I don't know. I don't know.
-[grunts]
-Did we make it in time?
[shushes]
[muttering]
-Oh, what the f--
-Oh, shit.
Dude.
I-I'm on it.
-Oh.
-[groaning]
Oh, God.
Oh, my God. Wait. Wait. Look. Look.
[cheering]
-Oh, my God. Holy shit. We did it.
-Oh, my God. [chuckles]
Oh, my God!
[whistles] Hey, losers!
Who here can remember just one year ago
when every blog and tech rag and pundit
told us that Tinder wasn't gonna make it?
[booing]
Well, today we have one million reasons
why they can shove it up their asses.
-[cheering]
-Tonight we celebrate.
Everyone go home and get dressed,
you all look insane and beautiful.
-Stephanie! Stephanie!
-Hold on. Yes?
I want you to invite the whole town.
I'm on the phone with the fire department.
After that then.
Then I should probably
call the insurance company.
[cheering]
They can't stop us now!
What the fuck? Hey! What the fuck?
You guys are animals! You're animals!
Tinder shots! Tequila!
Viagra! And Rohypnol!
-Oh shit! [laughs]
-[gasps] Diego!
Oh, my God!
[sighs] Thank you.
[chuckles]
He's crazy. [sighs]
Do you work here?
[grunts] Yeah, yeah.
I've been here since the beginning.
I'm, I'm Whitney.
[stammers] Marta.
But I-I'm just a plus one. [chuckles]
-Oh.
-[chuckles]
Oh, what's it like, uh, working here?
Feels like a real bro zone. [chuckles]
[chuckles] Yeah.
Uh, no it's going great. Thank you.
I mean, it's pretty all-consuming.
Um… you know we're together all the time.
It's kind of like a big…
it's a big family. You know? [chuckles]
Yeah. [inhales sharply] You know,
families can get messy. [chuckling] Right?
[chuckles]
It's great. It's going great.
Um, it was really nice to meet you.
Um… I gotta run.
-Bye.
[gasping, clamoring]
Holy moly! Oh, my God!
Okay. We need champagne.
I will be right back.
You must be famous Whitney Wolfe.
Oh. I'm not… I'm not sure
about that first part but yes.
Andrey Andreev. CEO of Badoo.
We are, uh,
biggest online dating platform in--
In all of Europe. [chuckles]
Yes, hi.
And as of a month ago,
all of South America.
Well, depending on
how you look at the numbers.
-Let's look at the numbers that way.
-[chuckles] Aren't you, um,
based out of London?
Yes, but uh… I keep office in the Bay
and uh… when I get
the invitation this afternoon,
I-I jump in the helicopter
and come down. Why not?
I was gonna take my chopper here too but,
you know, it's in the shop so…
They can be very temperamental.
-I found this to be true.
-Oh no. I was…
-I don't…
-You make a joke. I also make a joke.
-[chuckling] Oh.
-I know that I am very rich.
-That is my burden to bear.
-[chuckles]
But listen I want to be
very up-front with you.
This is not a chance interaction.
I know that you are the brains
behind this, uh…
[blows raspberry] This Tinder explosion.
[chuckles] Wow, uh, no.
This, this was a team effort.
No. Marketing, college campus strategy,
even the name.
My people tell me this was you.
Come be my CMO.
Uh…
Tinder have one million users,
start with very little.
It's not bad.
This is okay. But, uh, Badoo?
We have 377 million users.
190 countries.
Now we are biggest
online dating platform in the world.
But, uh, not yet
household name in America.
-Hmm? This is where Whitney Wolfe come in.
-[chuckles]
Hmm?
Wow, um… [sighs]
Badoo is… it's already Badoo.
So any success I might have there
could never feel fully mine.
I'm, you know…
Tinder is literally my whole world.
Tinder is, uh, great,
big dream cake for you, huh?
I know this probably sounds just crazy
but, um… I, I can't take you up
on your very generous offer.
Hmm.
Then I will crush you and your company.
-Just kidding. I make another joke.
-[chuckling]
No. This, this is your baby.
You, you want to stay?
I would do the same. But, uh…
You can't blame a girl for trying.
-[chuckles]
-And now I must leave you.
There are very many beautiful women here
and, uh… having your
own helicopter has its perks.
[chuckles] I bet it does. [sighs]
-Hey, how are you?
-Hey.
All right. [sighs] Oh, my God.
[sighs]
Hey, Whit.
Who the hell were you
talking to out there?
I don't know what you mean.
Oh, God.
I don't care what you do
outside of the company. I really don't.
But when you bring your boyfriends
around here, we got a problem.
-Oh, my God. Justin…
-No, I'm serious, I'm serious.
Okay, if you hurt my pride,
y-you will be fired.
-It's as simple as that.
-Oh, my God.
Okay, please.
I do not wanna do this at work.
You're telling me
not to bring our shit to work?
You're the one playing victim to Sean.
No, no, no. I just wanted him
to ask you to stop
-because, you aren't listening to me.
-And you thought he would side with you?
Heard you cried to him
about the Time article too. Is that true?
Oh, boy.
Having a female co-founder
makes us look like a joke.
[breathes shakily]
If you talk to me
about anything besides work from now on,
-it will not be good for you.
-[chuckles] Scary. Very scary.
Oh, God.
[breathes shakily]
-No, not really.
-What does that even mean?
She's like a… She's just,
I don't know, she's young. She's immature.
You were the one who slept with her.
I'm not saying…
[breathes shakily]
Yeah.
[Diego] Hey, Justin. There's the whore.
[laughing]
What?
Oh, uh, I-I don't…
Whitney, hey.
Um… not a great time. What's up?
[sighs]
Dude, please tell me
this isn't about you and Justin.
You know I don't
wanna bring you into this. [pants]
Yeah. Uh, yeah,
you mentioned that last time.
Sean, okay you… you know me.
It's okay. I do. I do.
What… Hey, hey. What's going on?
-This just, um… [breathes deeply]
-[laughing]
-…this is just all feeling a little…
-Come, just sit down here.
This is just feeling
really out of control. [sighs]
Yeah. What's going on?
He's, uh, cutting me out of meetings.
Um, he's… [sighs]
…he's sent me a thousand more texts
since the last time we talked.
Horrible texts.
I was just…
They just called me a whore,
um, in front of a bunch of people.
People I have to work with every day.
And he gets them to laugh with him at me.
It's unprofessional. It's affecting
my work, it's affecting his.
It's humiliating.
It's… It's… I cannot take it anymore.
If you can just ride this out
-and tough it out a little bit longer.
-Sean, no.
He's gonna get over it.
I'm telling you, I know him.
I-I cannot work here with him.
I can't.
Okay.
-[sighs]
-Okay. Okay.
[sighs]
So are you telling me
that you are resigning?
I mean you said that
you can't work here, right?
-I did, yeah.
-[sighs]
Okay.
Um, so you need to e-mail me
saying that you are quitting
and I need you to give a reason,
which I presume is because you want to
move to Texas to start your own company.
-I know that you've mentioned that.
-Sean, why are you doing…
Don't, don't treat me like a stranger.
-Sean, please.
-Your employment continuing here
is not likely an option at this point.
-So just send the e-mail.
-Why are you being all weird and lawyery?
You will be paid through
the end of the week
and IT can help with any and all
out-boarding that needs to take place.
Obviously if you need an employer
reference, you can speak to Stephanie
and she'll sort you out
and put it on my my letterhead.
-[gasps]
-[echoing] Any meetings you have
scheduled will be automatically suspended.
We'll need to get a refund on
flights and lodging
for that upcoming conference,
but we can handle that on our end.
Your password to the portal will expire,
um, automatically at midnight tonight.
[speaks indistinctly]
No. I do not want to sign an NDA.
Okay. Well, this settlement's gonna
be a nonstarter for them without the NDA.
I don't under… I don't understand. I, um…
when we filed the suit, you know,
you said we had a strong case.
And we do. You demonstrated a pattern of
abuse that is systemic and company-wide.
Right.
And the picture these text messages paint,
well, Justin Mateen wouldn't exactly
cut a sympathetic figure for a jury.
I mean he was suspended.
Which is why we were able to
get this settlement figure so high.
No, the money is nothing.
It's not nothing to me,
it's a crazy amount to me,
but for them it is a slap on the wrist.
I just want what I deserve.
I built Tinder with them.
I'm a… I'm a fucking co-founder.
-They contest that interpretation.
-[grunts]
-[sighs]
-[Robert] Whitney,
you want to take this to court,
we take it to court.
-This is your decision.
-[sighs] Okay.
What would that look like?
Well, we'll be spending
a lot more time together.
They have the resources to
drag this out three, four, five years.
And if this becomes a public trial,
uh, you have to think about
how you'll be perceived.
For Tinder, uh, a suit like this
will certainly be a blemish
on their reputation, but you… [sighs]
…you will always be that woman who
sued Tinder for sexual discrimination.
It will follow you.
And if history is any indication…
[sighs] …it will define you.
Even if you win.
[scoffs]
There's a reason less than 15% of
these cases go to trial.
Signing gives you the freedom to
move on to the next chapter of your life.
We did not discriminate
against Whitney in any way.
Now, I've learned
a lot through this process.
Guys, I recognize, yeah,
I could've handled things better.
But we take gender equality
very seriously here.
And none of this bullshit
is gonna slow us down.
-[cheers] Yeah, yeah.
-Okay?
Whitney Wolfe? Do you regret starting
a relationship with Justin Mateen?
-What?
-[Robert] Someone leaked the settlement.
How? [breathes shakily]
How did it get out?
Well, we know it wasn't us
and there's only one other party
that had access and opportunity.
But that's completely speculative.
We have no proof.
Well, now I get to tell
my side of the story.
Unfortunately, this leak does not
absolve you from the NDA.
How is that even possible?
So they can just write anything they want
about me and I have to stay silent?
-Anything they want?
-If you say anything, they can sue.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
[sighs] This is Marta Medina
[Jessica] Hi. It's Jessica.
You e-mailed me last week.
Um, thank you for, for getting back to me.
Yeah, I don't wanna go on record at all.
Um… But those guys.
They deserve to go down.
For a bunch of things.
D-Do you have any documentation?
I don't want anything coming back to me,
but you said you looked
into Magic Lab, right?
It's impossible to untangle
all the different subsidiaries.
It's not just the shell companies, it's…
it's just kind of crazy there.
Um, you should really just talk
to some of the other women.
Hi. I'm so sorry I'm late.
You know how impossible it is
to get out of there sometimes.
No, I don't anymore actually.
Oh, I didn't, um, mean, like, um…
Sean is being forced to step down as CEO.
He didn't have to leave the company,
but, like, he has to step down.
[chuckles] Okay, that doesn't
help me get a job. So…
You're not gonna have a problem
getting a job, Whitney.
How many people
co-founded a top app at 24?
According to Tech Monthly,
former employees said that Wolfe never
held nor deserved her co-founder title.
I don't think it's healthy to be
memorizing the negative comments.
Have you Googled me?
I wouldn't hire that insane person either.
I'm sorry. It's really unfair.
It's not so unfair that you'd
have a problem still working for them.
I know you don't think
that I should quit my job.
No, I'm not… No, no, no.
You do whatever is good.
If you feel good
working for them then… [exhales sharply]
You didn't seem to have
such a problem with them, Whit,
when that situation
was working in your favor.
Oh… [scoffs, chuckles]
You do not know what it was like for me.
You were not in those meetings.
No, I wasn't.
How could I possibly know
what was happening?
Because once you climbed up the ladder,
you never reached back down.
Where the hell is all of this coming from?
It's not fucking new, Whitney.
-You're just too selfish--
-Oh, now you figure is the time
-to tear me apart when I am at my lowest.
-I'm not trying to tear you down.
But as your friend,
I would appreciate if you would
just acknowledge your…
your inherent… your…
Dude, it's just easier for you, Whit,
it just is. It's easier.
Oh, my God, if it has been
so fucking easy for me
then how come you're still
the one with the fucking job.
You know what,
I don't wanna do this actually.
-Okay.
-I need a break from the Whitney show.
[scoffs]
Enjoy your drink.
[customer] Bitch.
-Have you seen this?
-Yeah, man, she's crazy.
-[echoes] Can I help you?
-[breathes shakily]
[sobs, breathes heavily]
[breathes shakily]
[breathing heavily]
[breathes heavily]
[breathes shakily]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[sighing]
[breathes heavily]
[phone vibrates]
-Hello?
- [Andrey] Whitney.
-Andrey?
-You're very difficult to get hold of.
My people have been trying you,
text, e-mail. But, uh, nothing.
Oh. Uh, yeah, I've been really, um…
I've been busy.
I'm deep in R & D on a new project.
Okay, sounds good. Well, I'm in town
and, uh, you wanna meet
and talk the next steps?
-Next steps?
- Can you be at Los Angeles theater tonight
at, uh, eight o'clock? Uh, we see a show
and then, um, maybe we can chat.
Uh, Andrey, wait, um…
I am not at Tinder anymore.
Yes, yes, I know. I hear the whole story.
It sounds like, uh, bullshit.
But, uh, I'm very happy because
it means I can poach you more easily.
-You said at eight?
-Okay. See you then.
[sighs]
[driver] This is the address.
Yeah, sorry, can I just have a minute?
Uh, I already ended
the trip in the app, so… Yeah.
[sighs] Okay.
[Andrey] I'm sure you have seen the
show many times, but for me it was first.
Oh, no I hadn't seen it either.
Really? You are, uh, Mormon
and you did not see this funny show?
-I'm not Mormon.
-But you are from Utah?
[chuckles] Yeah, but they let
non-Mormons live there too.
You know, I don't actually think Mormons…
[inhales sharply] …they don't
really love the show.
Huh. Well,
great it all works out. [chuckles]
-You want, uh, wine?
-Uh, sure.
-Uh, this.
-Got it.
-Okay, time for Mr. Straight To Point.
-[sighs]
What is this big, uh,
secret project you are developing, huh?
It's a social networking app
called Merci for women only.
Huh.
Yes and where the only currency…
the only way to communicate
will be through compliments, kindness.
Okay. But, uh…
Really I want you and me to do something
that we do best, you know? Dating app.
[scoffs] No. Hmm. There's no way.
I cannot go back into dating.
But, yes you can.
I read the court documents.
There is no non-compete clause.
It's crazy business.
[chuckles] I know. I mean, I…
I wanna work on
something I can be proud of.
[sighs] Actually, you know, do some good.
[sighs] That's very… very noble,
but, uh, are you sure that you want to
do this with a kindness app? [scoffs]
[chuckles] Um…
Okay, Andrey…
Listen, when I was a… a freshman,
I was the only girl in
my computer science class
and… [chuckles] …I remember
one day I walked in and I just…
Like, there was this giant photo of
a naked woman on the projector
and at first I thought, you know,
they're playing some kind of
prank on me obviously.
But it turned out the professor
had projected the photo
-Wow.
-It was Lena Forsén,
the 1972 Playboy centerfold.
Just happens to be the first image
ever digitally transferred.
It wasn't some kind of joke.
It was a lesson.
-In the foundation of computing history.
-Hmm.
The Internet is supposedly some
kind of transformative revolution, right?
Freedom. Democratization. You know?
But according to whom?
Apple. Amazon. Facebook. Twitter.
The rules of online behavior
have been written exclusively by men.
[chuckles] And the result is that
most of the online experience
is pretty fucking shitty for women.
Maybe we can fix this problem…
with dating.
[chuckles] Oh, my… Come on, Andrey,
everything that is wrong
with Internet culture
is at its peak with online dating.
It is regressive, it is full of creeps
who can spam,
harass women night
and day with no accountability.
It reinforces outdated
gender roles and… [sighs]
We need to change dating.
There it is. I knew you'd come up with
something great.
A dating app that is actually
a good experience for women.
-Like the Merci version of dating.
-Yes.
-Exactly. Made by women for women.
-Yes! [inhales sharply]
Wait… Um…
Just to be clear…
[sighs] I am not for hire.
Okay, uh… whatever this is…
-[sighs] I need to be the founder…
-Of course.
…and CEO.
Maybe you want, uh,
my helicopter too. Huh? [chuckles]
[chuckles] Sure. Why not?
Whitney this is your ship.
Captain Whitney.
-[laughs]
-[speaking Russian]
[employees shouting, clamoring]
Hey. [sighs] Can I walk you to your train?
It's gonna be here in two minutes.
Okay. [sighs] Uh, I'll keep it short.
Well, short for me.
Um…
Okay, listen, I'm sorry, all right?
The last time I saw you I was…
You were right, okay?
Look, I'd… I ignored how bad it was
there until all of this happened to me.
And I, I bought into the idea that there
was only space for one woman in the room.
And I made sure it was me.
And the… the worst part is I liked it.
It felt cool
being the only girl in the club.
[sighs] And it wasn't just that
I didn't push back on the toxic shit.
I-I'd feed into it to prove I could hang.
[sighs]
Tish, I've had some real blind spots.
I need to do better. I will.
Okay? I'm sorry. Okay?
You really pissed me off.
[sighs] I know.
-Like a lot.
-I know.
But…
I appreciate the apology.
And I'm sorry that
I couldn't be there for you
in the ways that
you really needed me to be.
[chuckles]
[Whitney chuckles, sighs]
-[chuckles]
-I mean, I kind of owe you anyway.
You've been to, like, every single one of
my shows even though we suck so bad.
No.
-Don't lie to my face.
-[chuckles] I thought, like…
I thought we just, like,
had a moment. [chuckles]
Okay. Listen, Tish.
I'm starting something new.
And, you know what? It's gonna be
empowering and intersectional.
Intersectional, new vocab.
[chuckles] Okay, it's fully funded,
and I need you to come and work with me.
-Yeah. Obviously I'm in.
-I understand if you need more time.
-No, I need zero time.
-And we…
-I'm giving those bastards zero notice.
-We would be relocating to Austin, Texas.
-I love Austin. Lets be weird, lets do it.
-It's the fastest growing city
-in the country and--
-Whitney!
Let's fucking do it.
-[chuckles]
-Let's go. Let's go. Let's do it.
["Shut Up and Let Me Go" playing]
[Whitney] Okay. What's the-the thing?
Our identity, you know?
We're missing that one, big hook.
The thing that we're missing is a name.
I really think that Bumble is a winner.
Oh, I don't… I don't know. I just…
I think of like, bumbling, stumbling.
Let's just keep talking big picture.
Okay, uh, banning harassment.
How do we actualize it?
Um, like a report feature.
Kind of like Twitter's.
It's just that… [sighs]
When I was going through the worst of it,
I was reporting tweets left and right.
And the next day, the same creep
would just be right back at it.
All right. So we need
a zero tolerance policy.
You harass once
and you're booted forever. Bye.
Yes, I love it. No second chances. Got it.
Yeah. And can we do
no unsolicited dick pics?
-Mmm. Yes.
-[Whitney] Absolutely.
-And I was also thinking some--
-And we should really create…
Sorry. Please.
Oh. Uh, no. That's fine.
Yeah. I was just, um,
I was thinking no shirtless selfies.
'Cause, you know, people,
they think Tinder,
and they think one-night stands,
and really cheesy shirtless selfies.
So, it's, like, um,
you want a fuckboy, use Tinder.
But you want something more,
like a meaningful relationship,
or even just like a decent person to bang,
uh, come on over to…
We need a name.
-Yeah. Come on over to our app…
-Careful. It's really hot.
-Thank you.
-…where you'll find better people,
or at least, um, better behaved people.
But, I don't know.
Oh. No. No, no, no, no.
Beth. Beth, I love it. We're doing it.
-[chuckles] Okay.
-Okay.
And while we're at it, uh,
no photos of people holding guns.
Okay. So, keep your shirt on and your gun
locked up and your dick in your pants.
It's so cool that we can just say stuff,
and then, it's real.
Also, every start-up
I've ever worked at was 90% dudes.
Right. Oh, so, we will hire
a 90% female team here in Austin.
-Can't do that.
-[gasps]
David. I forgot that you were back there.
You can't discriminate based on sex.
Well then, why is
every other start-up all men?
Look, let me rephrase.
You can't explicitly discriminate
-based on sex when hiring. Legally.
-[chuckles]
Okay. So, we won't explicitly hire
a 90% female team.
You can't say it like that either.
-[Whitney] Okay.
-[Andrey] Hello, ladies.
-[Tisha gasps] Andrey.
-[Andrey] Hello.
-[all] Hi.
-Wow. There's a big wave of energy
from the room there. This is… It's great.
So there's someone
I want you to meet. This is Charlotte.
-She's new PR person. She know everything.
-Hi.
-Hi, Charlotte.
I've heard a lot about you,
and I'm so excited to come down there,
see the operation in person sometime soon.
-Thank you.
-We can't--
-Oh.
-She is very expensive.
she charge me a lot of money per word,
so I-I cut off.
Um, but I see whiteboard.
A lot of ideas there.
Can I set a meeting with the engineers,
uh, get things started going?
Oh, no. No, no.
We're still missing something big here.
Including the name of the company.
And we just… We need a feature, right?
That just in no uncertain terms says
that we are here and we are different
and we are a hell of a lot better
-than anything you've tried before.
-Yes. Yes.
But have monumental breakthrough
very quickly.
You know I have board here,
very itchy to-to start monetizing.
-Yeah.
-All right. I know it's hard to have,
uh, big idea in this shitty little room.
Uh, you know, you get out see new city.
Try the local cowboy drinks.
-Okay.
-Only if David comes with us.
-[Whitney] Oh, yeah.
-[Tisha] David?
[Whitney] Oh, yeah.
Oh. It-It's almost my bedtime.
-Uh. David.
-David, come on.
-[Whitney] You can come.
-Well… [stammers]
-Come on.
-David.
-[chanting] David. David. David.
-No. There's no way.
- David. David.
- David. David. David.
I can't believe David didn't come.
Yeah, it really seemed like
that chanting was gonna work.
[patrons cheering]
[upbeat country music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
Whit. Um, there's a guy who I think
is checking you out over there.
I don't wanna talk guys. I wanna talk app.
I think we should go with Bumble.
Come on. It's, like… Okay.
Uh, bumblebees, right?
The app becomes your hive.
And what is at the center of a hive?
-The queen bee.
-Exactly.
It's female-centric.
It's inclusive and safe.
It's literally everything that
we've been looking for.
Um, Whit. That cute cowboy at the end
of the bar keeps looking over here.
[sighs] I really don't have time for guys.
We need to focus on Bumble.
Thank you. It's good.
-Perfect.
-I hear you, but I think you should…
-Jesus.
-Mm-hmm.
[Whitney] Whoo.
-[chuckles]
-Yeah.
[chuckles] You know, I mean, I don't know.
I, um, haven't been out with anyone
since my life imploded.
Yeah. Well, it's time to
get back on that horse.
Or maybe just on the cowboy.
But what if the guy googles me?
Come on. What is he gonna see?
Like, a thousand articles saying
that I might be a lying whore.
That's something that
you can bring up on a second date.
-Or maybe even a third.
-Or we could not play
three-dimensional chess and just focus
on this palpable sexual tension.
-Oh, yeah. Give him some signals.
-Wow.
Come on. Maybe he'll come over here.
Maybe I just go introduce myself.
-Yeah.
-Oh, I don't know.
I feel, like, it's better
if he comes over here.
You don't want to
come off as, like, desperate.
-Desperate? What do you mean?
-Listen, I don't think that. It's…
I-I think… Some people think that. Um…
You know, like,
that the guy should come to you.
[Tisha] Mmm.
[stammers] I…
Um… Wait… I need a, um…
Okay. We have a lot to discuss, but first,
I gotta see a man about a beer.
-Okay.
-Okay, good.
That's good. I'm glad she's doing that.
[mellow country music playing]
Hi.
Hi. [chuckles] Hi, I'm Michael.
Um, can I… Can I buy you a drink?
Oh, well, that depends. Um…
Will you just read this article about me?
And then you can just let me know
if you're still interested.
Uh, yeah. Yeah, all right.
-Thanks. [chuckles]
-Yeah, sure.
-Whitney.
-Yes.
Got it. Yeah. Okay.
Oh.
[inhales sharply] Yeah, sorry.
I-I don't think, uh,
I can buy you a drink, after all.
Yeah. Yes.
Yeah, because according to the article,
you've got a million dollars.
Which means you should be
buying me a drink.
[Whitney chuckles]
Yeah, that can be arranged.
-Um, should I sit? Yes, I'll sit.
-Yeah. You wanna sit? Yeah, please sit.
How can we create an online space
that feels safe and empowering, right?
Which leads us to our core principle…
Women make the first move.
When members of the opposite sex
match on Bumble,
women have to send the first message.
This is gonna shift
outdated gender dynamics,
encouraging equality from the get-go.
[Bumble team talking indistinctly]
-Come on y’all, download Bumble!
-[Bumble team cheering]
-Let's talk about reprogramming.
-But with respect,
why reprogram code that's already working?
This is not a plug-and-play
of your existing product and API.
We need to use thoughtful UX UI,
innovative machine learning models,
very secure backend infrastructure
and new safety systems to build
the safest place on the Internet
for women.
You heard her.
Hey, what have we got?
So Tinder's parent company is
suing Bumble for trademark infringement.
Why, drama just follows this woman around.
Maybe this time she'll buzz off.
We swipe left
on your past attempts to buy us.
on your current attempts to intimidate us.
No comment.
Instead of focusing on us,
you should spend your time taking care
of bad behavior on your own platform.
[no audible dialogue]
Which is why we are so, so, so proud
to invest in BIPOC female founders.
But the laws haven't caught up
with this new reality.
We need accountability for bad behavior.
If indecent exposure is
a crime on the streets,
then why is it okay
on your phone or computer?
-Let me know if this feels all right.
-I appreciate it.
-Good right here?
-How's it looking out there?
One sec.
Okay, baby, you have all day. [chuckles]
You really don't need to put that on now.
Yeah, good. 'Cause I think
this is gonna take all day anyways.
-[chuckles]
-Okay, Whitney, let's check levels.
You could rehearse
whatever you're gonna say tonight.
-Okay.
-No, no. She's more of a wing-it gal.
[chuckles] Okay, something like:
After a billion romantic matches,
our new feature, Bumble for Friends,
um, is the culmination of everything
I have been working towards.
[Michael] Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
BFF will transform our company
into a community-driven,
-female forward social network.
-Yeah.
-Sounding great. Thank you, Whitney.
-[chuckles]
-You're gonna crush it.
-Okay. I am taking this…
-Thank you.
-…because I know you don't wanna wear it.
-I hate it. I hate it so much.
-[phone dings]
-Oh.
Okay.
All right, I have to go back to the office
for another interview.
-[Michael] Mm-hmm. It's fine.
-Sorry. Um, but I will see you tonight?
-Yes.
-Love you.
Hi. Hi, I'm Whitney.
Uh, Marta Medina. Forbes.
Um, well, welcome.
Uh, you are here during,
probably what is the most exciting week.
[Marta chuckles]
Oh, we've met before.
-At a Tinder party years ago.
-[chuckles]
-You remember that. [chuckles]
-Oh, well, you know.
I don't forget faces or names,
or anything really.
Well I…
Yeah, I knew there was a story there,
but I-I-I got scooped by, uh…
By your lawsuit.
I'm not legally allowed to comment
on my time at Tinder.
I wish you would've discussed it then.
Maybe I do too.
You know what?
We're here to talk about Bumble BFF.
What can I tell you?
Uh, well, I'm… I'm actually here
to talk about something else.
Oh, okay.
[stammers] A piece I've written about
your current parent company.
Badoo or Wide Vision or MagicLab,
depending on which tax shelter
we're referring to.
Um… I'm sorry, I don't think I understand.
This is the article.
It goes live at 5:00 p.m. today.
I'm here to give you a chance to comment.
[stammers] [exclaims]
[stammers] I'm sorry, I don't… Um…
[stammers] I'm sorry. This doesn't…
No, this doesn't make sense.
[exclaims] I thought it would
after everything you've been through.
Oh. No, no, no. Those guys were…
Um, Andrey is… I mean, he's…
Bumble wouldn't exist without Andrey.
[stammers] No, he's… He's always been
a supporter of us and women.
-And he--
-People can be more than one thing.
I have never seen Andrey
take part in any of this stuff.
He's an advocate. He's my friend.
Is that your comment?
This is so fucking awful.
All the major outlets
will be in there tonight.
-And they are gonna want answers.
-We could cancel.
Look, we spent months
on a multimillion-dollar BFF rollout.
There is gonna be thousands of people
filing into the theater
in less than an hour.
You could open with an acknowledgement.
Acknowledge what?
The drugs, sleaze and misogyny
or the sexism, racism and tax evasion?
-Well, all of it.
-[chuckles]
-She's already commented.
-I said that Andrey was supportive,
-a good guy and my friend. Jesus.
-You told the truth.
-But I was caught completely off guard.
-Well, your instincts were good.
But it wasn't enough.
You should use tonight's platform.
Close with a strong unequivocal
statement of support for Andrey and Badoo.
If you do that this all can blow over.
Sorry, what? [chuckles]
All of this happened
on a completely different continent.
We shouldn't be doing anything
to bail out those assholes.
-It's not that simple.
-Of course it is.
Whitney. Think about all of these women
who've come forward for this story.
And think about
how the narrative is being framed.
Everything in this article is about Badoo
but Bumble is the name in the headline.
They're trying to drag you into this
because it is a better story.
Do not take the bait.
We need to stay out of it.
Okay, do that, and Bumble closes its doors
by the end of the week.
Badoo is not only your parent company,
they also own all your servers.
If they go down,
so does Bumble. Literally.
The majority of female founders
lose their company
within the first three years.
You told me that in our first meeting.
And that my job was
to protect you and your company.
So fight for what you've built.
Make the statement.
Whit, this is a bad idea.
We need to stay out of it.
I'll think about it.
Whitney. Hello.
[sighs] Hi.
It's a full house out there.
Uh… [clears throat] Very enthusiastic.
Thank you for, uh,
your words in the article.
-It means a lot.
-[scoffs]
I'm very sorry about…
[exclaims] …all of this.
No. How could…
How could you let this happen?
I was blindsided. [stammers]
The Forbes lady, she come
and pretend to be all nice girl,
but how could I know that
it would be a big press story.
I'm talking about what was in the story.
[exclaims] She exaggerates everything.
Okay, what exactly was she exaggerating?
Everything. I mean, come on,
the team, they work very hard.
And, sure, sometimes, okay,
they want to blow off the steam
and, uh, maybe they go
a little bit far. Okay?
Like, cocaine at a party with adults.
[stammers] Ooh, big story.
No, it is not a big story, okay?
And personally, I saw nothing, okay?
What about the prostitutes?
[stammers] The company
never paid for any prostitutes.
[sighs] I just…
How do you think a female employee
feels at one of these parties?
Where male employees are
openly getting blow jobs.
Yeah… [stammers] It was different time.
It was four months ago.
[sighs] Look, it's a very big
wake up call, okay?
And-and we change many many policies but…
Look, you have been around
long enough to know that
this behavior is not very out of the norm.
But we're not supposed to be the norm.
Bumble was created to be
a rebuke of this toxic bullshit.
-You are destroying all of that.
-[stammers] But put in perspective, okay?
Badoo has been put in this, uh,
American Me Too stuff.
It is ridiculous. It's not fair.
Okay, what about Jessica?
Your CMO, who was asked to give
a male job applicant
a massage to sweeten the deal.
That a part of her job was to look sexy?
[sighs] Is that why
you offered me that job?
Whit, no. Come on. I…
You and me… [stammers] …we have
worked together, side by side,
for a long time.
And have I ever treat you with anything
but respect and-and dignity?
No.
No, so, you know that
I am not a-a bad guy.
[sighs]
This is… [stammers]
This is big lesson for me.
And I will change culture at Badoo.
I promise you.
What you have done already for women,
it goes so far beyond, uh, dating.
We can move forward, we can grow,
we can change the world, okay?
Captain Whitney. [chuckles]
From position of strength.
But first, we… we must, uh,
push past this together,
and-and-and we can move on.
[audience applauding, cheering]
Well, it can be really hard to
make new friends as an adult.
You know, we've gotten to the point
where it's easier to go on a date
than it is to make a friend.
[chuckles] Okay. Speak for yourself.
[audience laughs]
Um, you can use Bumble BFF to,
uh, find a movie buddy, uh, grab a coffee,
grab a smoothie, walk your dog.
Whatever you want.
Even start a business.
Uh, I love that.
A woman in business getting
more women in business.
We need those kinds of champions.
Isn't that cool?
[audience cheering]
You know… Um…
[smacks lips] Sometimes that can be
harder than it seems, in all honesty.
[stammers] Now, I haven't always
been great at women.
Sometimes I've been guilty of, you know…
laughing at sexist remarks or…
You know, putting other women down
to make myself feel like I was
the cool, smart one at the table.
Well, now that you have some perspective,
you're using those lessons
to fight sexism and inequality.
Hmm. I could be doing more.
You're a 30-year-old running
an incredibly successful
feminist business.
I would actually
just like to say something
about my partnership…
with Badoo and Andrey Andreev.
[audience murmuring]
I feel saddened…
And honestly, I'm sickened to hear
what has transpired at Badoo.
[whispers] I don't think you…
I want to acknowledge that
me not personally seeing the bad behavior
in no way negates or excuses it.
No one deserves to be marginalized
or mistreated in the workplace.
Accountability is not something you can…
[audience murmuring]
[scoffs]
Accountability is not something that
you can reason your way out of.
If you don't condemn it,
you are supporting it.
I will not stand for toxic behavior.
[murmuring intensifies]
Is it still…
Crazy in there? Yeah.
And Badoo's stock fell 15% on the Nikkei.
[clicks teeth]
Sorry.
I'm not.
[chuckles]
Oh.
Howdy.
-You did good.
-[blows raspberry]
I just blew up my life.
Let's get you home.
Whoo!
-[laughs]
-[chuckles]
[sighs]
[knock on door]
Hey. Sorry. I don't mean to just
show up on your doorstep,
but I felt it best to have
this conversation in person.
-I'm Matthew--
-Matthew Slate.
Uh, Blackstone Investment Group.
So, to get right to it,
Blackstone's bought out Andrey.
Okay. Of what exactly?
Everything. We're about to become
majority shareholders
of Badoo, Magic Lab and Bumble.
It's not official for two or three weeks,
but in light of recent, um, events…
we feel it's a good time to
make changes. Drastic ones.
And fast.
If you're gonna sell off Bumble,
then I need to have the chance to raise
the capital to buy it from you first.
No. That's not gonna happen.
Bumble's far too valuable an asset.
[stammers] But your position,
that is something we need to discuss.
I won't step down without a fight.
No. That's not…
Uh, we want you to stay on, Whitney.
As CEO.
CEO of all of it.
Magic Lab, Badoo and Bumble.
There's no more-qualified candidate.
You start as soon as possible.
In that case, I have a few ideas.
Already. [chuckles]
Well, that's great.
Um, we have ideas as well.
-First, we'll--
-Matthew. How about I go first?